the big b swarm is coming
hcbbs hermitcraft big b swarm
what is going on h c b b s has just
taken over the set oh my goodness
there's a lot of bees
oh my word
people have gone nuts
what is this
oh man you have no idea how much
i want to just
boop that away i've never been so
tempted in my life i must resist and and
anyway welcome back to a new episode of
hermitcraft we're actually on our way to
do something uh different i need to go
and save one of our fellow hermits from
lava look at this this is just in so
intriguing i've never been so distracted
okay we need to go and save one of our
fellow hermits from certain lava so this
happens occasionally people fall in lava
and they don't want to lose their stuff
so they log out and they're like hey can
someone come and save me from lava so
that's what we're up to at the start of
this episode and it seems that the
person stuck in lava today is doc on one
of his big mining sessions i just have
to figure out how to get down there
green's my no trespassing i don't
remember making this
oh man that oh
that is uh that is not a flattering
angle
turns out someone already saved him well
i guess back to the secret base then i
was totally gonna prank him
i was gonna save him from lava but i was
also gonna prank him so it's probably
best that someone else found him to be
honest but anyway with a big three two
one clap i'm not gonna dis i'm vanishing
again
right on three we're gonna end up back
in the secret base and hopefully
spring back into existence as well three
two one
and we're here
i need to figure out some better
transitions for this thing so today
i haven't actually done anything since
the last episode pretty much but today i
would like to make some huge progress
and i mean huge progress so
nothing has changed down here in the
sewers now someone did actually in the
comments bring up the issue
that what if corrales finds even one
tunnel one sewer tunnel or one of our
secret bases
then the whole thing
is ruined
and it's a pretty fair point so we're
gonna have to maybe do a little bit
better to conceal
each of these tunnels but sometimes
the fun has to outweigh the risk so
today i want to start off by preparing
the area for the sewer to be created b
dubs and i are going to collaborate on
this and maybe some other people as well
but in order to build something you've
got to make the space for it that's the
issue with building underground you
gotta you gotta do a lot of mining so
let's get started on preparing this area
for the sewer system
[Music]
we have dug a pretty big space and it's
amazing that we didn't hit anything in
the city bdubs came and helped me out
impulses come and help me out and i've
also seen that scar has just joined as
well all right let's meet up with b dubs
and scar
and let's get this thing made welcome
scar
come on in
oh man
from the security up above make sure you
cut that out of your video secrets
secrets oh yeah yeah don't show that
don't show that we can't we can't trust
anyone so don't show the iron golem trap
yeah no no no no don't show anything
no no no no none of it none of it
welcome to what is currently absolutely
nothing but a giant hole
what we want to make here
is kind of like a sewer
village and as you can see we kind of
started the terrain there b dubs kind of
jumped the gun before we started the
time lapse i'm very excited
we're gonna do like a cool uh trick with
glass to make it look like sewage
it looks nicer than it sounds like we're
gonna do this really cool trick with the
glass
and we're basically gonna make our
little society down here and um yeah the
plan is once that's made call a meeting
of everyone that's made a secret base as
far as i'm aware it's
scar b dubs me and impulse but i did
send other invitations out i'm just not
sure whether they've actually accepted
them or not and the invitation said
we're gonna become sewer people and this
is the sewer basically yeah so what if
you've got your secret base then all you
got to do is link it up to here via a
sewer system and then yeah you're part
of the gang and then i i'm not spoiling
it but i've got i got super big plans
and when this place is built then i will
share it with everyone
did we get to know off camera or or are
we just going to be healthy
no suspense absolute suspense but this
is actually i think one of the first
builds of the season that we've done
properly collaboratively we've been down
hall together
but yes it's another this is i'm excited
it's rare i usually do the time lapses
alone so if you guys want to help excuse
me yes breaking things
let's start with sleep
a little bit of sleep no building not
breaking
oh bro
nice job
all right i'm back geez i only have two
hearts left now geez louise
okay you ready to start this time lapse
let's go
[Music]
welcome sewer cats
we are the sewer cats and are the sewer
cats
i think i think scars cat wins it you
look like
i don't even know i think with the suit
and everything it's perfect i love it
i'm a very grouchy villain yes your
grumpy cat yeah nothing's gonna work out
for me in my villain it just
wasn't a good time i want to say a
massive thank you for everyone because
every everyone pitched in to make this
happen uh all the different times but
check it out this is our new home this
is the sewer and i'm pretty i'm pretty
confident corrales won't find this it's
not it's not where he'd expect it at all
so i think we're all i think we're
pretty safe here and i want to introduce
you all into the whole reason why we're
doing this and this little sign over
here
the corrales games
this this is what i've been thinking
forget the secret bases like you know
krause is gonna find those
this is what it's all about the corrales
games so
basically the goal is to mess with
corrales as much as possible without
getting caught
all right so i've got some ideas of what
we can do like move parts of the city
into the sewer scare corrales make him
laugh add graffiti trap corrales and
then i'm thinking we give each other
points based on how good the thing is
that we did you you three all just
looked at me at exactly the same time
[Laughter]
we like contests that's why
i've got no prizes but it's just it's
just the corrales games i think i think
this could be a lot of fun question yes
do we have to wear these cat heads no
i don't even know where you guys got
these cat heads from
it's a thing now we're we're the sewer
cats
they're making me feel good
scar
yeah
so i was thinking we should kick this
thing off corrales is actually not
online now so why don't we all
kick this thing off let's all head over
into the city
grab something move it down into the
sewers and here's the thing if you get
caught or corrales notices what's
missing you lose those points and you've
got to put it back
okay so that's the key we have to pay
attention to what he might not miss or
what he will miss but obviously the more
daring you go
the more points you're gonna get so why
don't we try all this out head up to the
to the city and grab something each yeah
don't point don't stop don't yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah or show how we get in and
out
we're in the sky a build limit
yes i'm gonna need to follow one of you
guys out i'm i'm gonna get lost forever
yeah the joke's on you there is no
entrance and exit so this is gonna be
fun
right i'm gonna i'm taking this
everyone got their thing from the city
yes i do all right add it to the sewer
and then we're going to dish out the
points based on how daring we think it
is
okay just pop it down anywhere yeah just
hold first
okay okay okay are we gonna score these
points i'm gonna go over here um i'm
gonna i'll build mine first and then and
then we'll go and review
okay mine's mine's super not that
interesting but i'm pretty sure he won't
notice a bunch of his hay going missing
okay
hey bales hey bails
a giant city i'm a dozen really you want
to give me you just take it
point five no zero no no point five
points oh come on okay
fair enough i did expensive i went very
conservative on my first one okay i
didn't want to i want to lose the game
immediately okay i don't want to pop
this mark yeah yeah yeah yeah right what
have you guys got i got half a point
here i grabbed um a little advertisement
the beacons back in stock at lamps plus
i think
wait wait wait
wait
i i actually gave this to him
disqualified
impulse built that
was
[Laughter]
dude i'm in the lead with half a point
because that's not even
zero she's
disqualified disqualified fine fine
you'll see me wait all right this is
where you guys go okay over here over
here i have this lovely wheel that i
borrowed from one of his vehicles just
one way there was five other wheels on
it so i thought he would be fine without
this one
it's not super daring zero point
uh i'll give you i'll give you one point
for this i think it's better than the
hay bales but oh it's
not super daring okay i'll take it i'm
winning all right scott what do you got
i'm over here i found an american flag
very patriotic okay i think that's also
a one pointer that's it's
oh
it's not it's not but it's not more
daring than the wheel it's less than the
wheel it's true it's primary colors you
notice these things all right okay
it was a small first round but we we
have to see if if corrales notices and
then we're going to ramp things up and
then don't forget that it's not just
moving stuff into the sewers we can
scare corrales
the most interesting one for me is make
corrales laugh if anyone can do that i
will dish out big points okay if you can
make karas laugh somehow and him not be
super suspicious i will i will dish out
the points for that one okay challenge
accepted all right we better keep score
this but uh let the corrales games begin
this is gonna be a lot of fun so the
points as they stand i'm on half a point
scar one impulse one beat up zero i mean
we didn't go big for this first one we
gotta we just gotta make sure that
corrales doesn't notice at first we're
gonna ramp things up like the pesky
birds we are or sewer cats i guess
so i'm proper excited for this
secret bases are one thing
the corrales games
are something else
something else
so the latest news is that there is
something going on
by the button two and we're about to
finally find out what what hcbbs
even means
there was a message on discord it's
happening
according to the message on discord we
are on the very final
lamp
so everyone's kind of congregating
because we don't know exactly when this
is gonna go off but look look at this
have you ever seen the server so busy
everyone that's thrown their name into
this and maybe people don't know what
this is but basically it's a random big
box
that clearly was made by mumbo thank you
reddit for busting that one
and
basically you just put your name in the
chest and you've signed up for something
we don't know hc bbs and there's all
sorts of societies like
hobbits and
bees
only on hermitcraft so
i guess we're gonna find out what this
is all about everyone's kind of got into
groups like there's a hobbit society and
we're kind of what's left so we're the
we're just the homeless we just want to
know what this thing is about and also
can i just i want to bring this up
because i saw on reddit that like mumbo
totally got busted for building this
thing because he left all the concrete
in his inventory on the episode that he
discovered it
so it's
it's good job mumbo
that's what i'm saying that's why
people you know exactly what's happening
right the button is coming back oh
yeah it's a second coming i love the
fact that mumbo has denied this by the
way he i don't think he's going to admit
it i don't think he's going to admit
that he made this but like it looks
exactly like the button and then he was
caught with all the different concrete
there's no denying it
it just creeps me out every morning
though
i can't find you wren oh
something's happening
okay
fireworks all right cool that's
extensive cool
oh wait the bottom has blown up the
bottom has blown up
why is this everybody's running
dude it's like a pinata get down here
there's probably free stuff okay well
dude
oh my goodness oh shoot
geez
[Laughter]
click the finger button
i'm so
do you guys want me to read this out
there's some signs okay hermic okay here
we go it's the hermitcraft big bass swap
oh
okay thank you for giving us the deeds
to your base in the form of a signed
submitted
before the deadline oh no your base has
now been transferred to another hermit
indefinitely
you have now been assigned a new base by
the hcbs
go up to your labelled box and see what
base you now own deeds can be
transferred between homes
[Music]
i don't know who i got can somebody
translate this my dyslexia is on 110
here yeah give it to me green just just
could you decipher that you know who
holds the deeds now owns the base i now
have mumbo and zed off space
that'll be three diamonds
i don't wanna live like a true king guys
hold on i have count literally three
times here we go
thank you you said this mumbo
yeah you got mumbo
we value mumbo's base at three diamonds
oh yes
this is crazy guys i'm sad i didn't get
in why you didn't get anyone what what
yeah i don't think i put my name down
so i better go and get my house in order
we're swapping
wow that first one was pretty small
[Applause]
that's a lot of chorus free food for
everyone
that was really satisfying oh my god
well
it looks like
we're swapping bases so i have two
questions
one
does anyone know where my new base is
and two
i'm not too worried about this we'll
figure out a way to get our deed back
somehow and to be honest with you i'm
kind of excited to let zeddaff just go a
little bit nuts see what he comes up
with his base is full of wacky
contraptions and to be honest that's
probably something that my base is
lacking
and um between you and i
i'm pretty happy that i don't have to
work on the back of the base
so this is going to be an awful lot of
fun and i'm very excited to see what
zeddaff is going to come up with
for
his i guess it's his base now so we'll
see what happens but don't worry
we'll figure a way to get back our deed
and zf i'm sure will want to figure out
a way to get his base back as well but
for now
let's see how this thing plays out
because
i don't know
nothing like this has happened this
season
and it's a it's a pretty big thing so i
don't know let's let's see where this
goes
so the last thing to say is thank you
very much for watching oh wait
do i need to show him where my secret
base is i'll figure that out okay so we
better say goodbye
to this base at least for the time being
i've got my my zeddaff deed over here so
this is no longer
my base
i'm probably gonna have a little chat
with zeddaff in the next episode just to
kind of uh finalize the base swap
and maybe just discuss
terms a little bit
i don't know what zenav's gonna do here
but let's just check that there's
i mean as long as he doesn't take down
the diamond chandelier i'm happy i don't
think he'd touch any of that stuff to be
honest like i said
the biggest relief
don't have to worry about this anymore
this is officially someone else's
problem but that's not to say
that i haven't got problems of my own
zf's base is probably
a little bit more unfinished than my
base
so i'm gonna have to try and figure out
how on earth i'm gonna bridge the gap
here this is a bit of a turn of events
i'm excited to see what we do but i
don't think there's anything i really
need to grab because all of my valuables
are in my ender chest and
you can't take that away from me so i
think i think we're pretty good on this
front man i guess
i guess this all belongs to zedf now at
least for the time being
so now i need to start brainstorming
well one i need to go and find zlf space
well my base and two i need to start
brainstorming
how on earth i'm gonna manage to trade
it back because i'm not go i don't blame
zed if he wants to keep hold of the
mansion
would you blame him because i don't we
need to figure out a really creative way
of getting zeddaf to trade back with us
somehow we need to trade these little
bits of paper
and see what happens
wait i've just had a thing we just spent
this entire episode making the sewers
and i think corrales has swapped with
someone i think we might need to rename
the corrales games
to the zombie clio games
we can get away with so much more now
this is so exciting
oh
next episode i need to go and record the
next episode right now but for now i
gotta go thank you very much for
watching everyone this is so exciting i
shall see you in the next episode where
everything's gonna get turned upside
down including me including clio's base
clio city
oh man the clio games just begun
alright so thank you very much for
watching and i shall see you in the next
very exciting episode good bye
you